gainsight.com 2017-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Customer Success Software | Gainsight

Gainsight, Inc. (“Gainsight”) owns and operates a service that allows its customers to access and use its proprietary customer success management platform (the “Service”) described in more detail at www.gainsight.com. At Gainsight, we feel strongly about protecting the privacy of individuals who visit our website or who use our Service.

This Privacy Policy applies to all information received by Gainsight through your use of our website or the Service. It informs you what information is collected, how we use this information, how we store it and under what circumstances we will disclose it to third parties. We collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which we do business. Gainsight currently operates as an independent U.S. corporation. Future subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with Gainsight will be required to adhere to this Privacy Policy as well.

This Privacy Policy also sets forth the privacy principles that Gainsight follows with respect to transfers of personal information here in the United States and between the United States and member states of the European Union, Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway (the European Economic Area, or “EEA”). Gainsight is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) and other U.S. authorized statutory bodies.

### DEFINITIONS

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you as an individual, for example your name, address, telephone number, email address, and any other information that can be combined to identify you. When you visit certain areas of our website, we may ask you for personal information if you request information about our Service, for example, if you request access to a demo or any of our online training materials, or if you request a download of a white paper or best practices guide.

Anonymous information is information that is collected about you as you use our website, but which does not identify you as an individual, or connect to your name, address, or any other personal information. Examples of anonymous information about you that might be collected on our website are the pages you visited, the length and time of your visit, the browser and operating system used, device type, geographic location, and the rate at which requested data was transferred to you. One method we use to collect anonymous information about you on our site is through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small data file that a website can send to your browser to be stored automatically on your computer. Cookies are commonly used to track your visits to a site so you don’t have to log in on every page and to analyze how you use the site. This allows website operators like Gainsight to serve you better.

 **PRIVACY SHIELD**. Gainsight complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Gainsight has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

**1\. NOTICE:** When Gainsight collects personal information from individuals in the EEA, we will inform them about the purposes for which this information is being collected and used, the types of third parties to which we may disclose such information, and the choices and means that we offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are first asked to provide personal information to Gainsight or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before we use the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected.

 **2\. CHOICE:** When Gainsight collects personal information from you, you have the opportunity to opt-out of having your information disclosed to a third party, or used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected by emailing us with your request at privacy@gainsight.com. If you choose to opt-out in this manner, your request will be processed immediately and take effect within 30 days.

 **3\. ONWARD TRANSFERS TO THIRD PARTIES:** Gainsight will use reasonable efforts to obtain assurances from its third party partners that they will safeguard personal information consistent with the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. Examples of appropriate assurances that may be provided by third party partners include a contract obligating the third party partner to provide at least the same level of protection for the personal information it has access to as is required by the Privacy Shield Principles or Privacy Shield certification by the third party partner. If we become aware that a third party partner is using or disclosing personal information in violation of this Privacy Policy, we will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. In cases of onward transfer of the data of EEA individuals to third party processors received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Gainsight is potentially liable for violations of the Privacy Shield Principles by such parties. Gainsight is partnered with Salesforce.com, Sendgrid, and Mandrill to support the performance of the Service by processing your personal information or the personal information of your customers as the same is downloaded by you into the Service platform. Gainsight is partnered with Salesforce.com, AWS, and Heroku to support the performance of the Service by processing your anonymous information in order to provide usage reports that you request and to optimize and enhance the Service.

 **4\. SECURITY:** Gainsight will take reasonable and industry standard precautions to protect personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

 **5\. DATA INTEGRITY AND PURPOSE LIMITATION:** Gainsight will only use personal information for the purpose for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, complete, and current.

 **6\. ACCESS:** Gainsight acknowledges that EU individuals have the right to access the personal information that we maintain about them. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to privacy@gainsight.com. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

 **7\. RECOURSE, ENFORCEMENT AND LIABILITY:** Gainsight will conduct compliance audits of its privacy practices to verify adherence to this Privacy Policy. Gainsight employees that are found to have violated this Privacy Policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of their employment with Gainsight.

 **COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION ON THE GAINSIGHT WEBSITE.** Gainsight collects some personal information and some anonymous information about you from our website in order to maintain the website and to tailor the website to your needs. We do not collect personal information that is connected to your online activities over time or across third-party websites or online services (but we may collect this type of anonymous information about you through the use digital re-targeting technology). We may use personal information collected through our website to complete a transaction you request. For example, to provide Gainsight business information to you that you have specifically requested. If you give us permission, Gainsight and its third party partners may also use your mailing address, telephone number or email address to alert you about updates to the Service or to discuss potential sales of the Service. If you give us permission to use your personal information for a specific purpose and you decide later you don’t want us or our third party partners to contact you, you have the ability to rescind your permission. Anonymous information collected through our website is used for maintenance and monitoring of the website, and market research.

 **COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION THROUGH THE GAINSIGHT SERVICE.** Gainsight collects some of your personal information, some of your customer’s personal information and some anonymous information in order to provide you with the Service. Gainsight may collect anonymous or personal information relating to your use of the Service, for example, your usage of the Service, renewal data and clickstream data. Anonymous information gathered from your use of the Service may be used in conjunction with personal information gathered at the same time to prepare reports for you on how you are using the Service. For example, we may gather information about how many times a specific user name in under your Service account uses a certain feature of the Service and for what length of time, and include the same in a report provided to you. Personal Information we collect from you or your customers through the Service is collected and used for the sole purpose of providing the Service to you. We also use personal information provided to us by you, or which you upload to the Service via the platform, in accordance with your authorization under the Terms of Service to assist you with questions and to resolve problems relating to your use of the Service. Gainsight uses anonymous information to efficiently operate the Service, to enhance your experience using the Service, to optimize the performance of the Service, and to show potential customers how the Service is used by other customers. For example, we may use anonymous information to diagnose and correct any problems you or others are having with the Service or include anonymous information in a Service usage report during a sales pitch to a potential customer to show how the Service is used by existing customers.

 **STORAGE OF INFORMATION.** Gainsight utilizes third party service providers to store personal information and anonymous information. Such providers are SSAE 16 certified and maintains a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your information. All Personal and Anonymous Information is stored on physically and electronically secured servers. Access to this information is strictly limited to individuals who have a legitimate reason to use the information. The information is protected with security industry best practices, including; network security controls, logical and physical access controls, segregation of duties, and the principle of least privilege to prevent unauthorized access. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of your data will not occur, we work hard to prevent such occurrences.

 **SECURITY OF INFORMATION.** Gainsight maintains a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information while it Is under our control, including the use of industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information. For example, your information resides on physically and electronically secured servers. We also use encryption technologies and other methods, depending on the type of information being transmitted or stored, to increase the security and privacy of information traveling to, from and within the Service. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of your data will not occur, we work hard to reduce the risk of such occurrences by storing the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. Although we take reasonable steps to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent all third-parties from obtaining your information.

 **SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES.** Gainsight does not sell, rent or lease any of your personal information to third parties without your express permission. Gainsight may disclose any of your information with or without notice to you if required by a subpoena, judicial or administrative order or as required by law, or where, in our sole discretion, we have a reasonable belief that it is necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the general public, to prevent a violation of the Gainsight Terms of Service Agreement or the rights of Gainsight or any third party. We may also be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger or acquisition of or with Gainsight and another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your information to the acquiring entity. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you by posting notice on our website or sending you an email regarding any such change in ownership, and you may choose to modify any of your information at that time.

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES.** This website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Gainsight. Please be aware that Gainsight is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy policies of every website that may collect your personal information. Gainsight is not responsible for personal information you provide to other such services or the privacy practices and other policies of such services.

 **QUESTIONS.** If you have any questions or comments about our use of your information or about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at [privacy@gainsight.com](mailto:privacy@gainsight.com).

 **UPDATING OR REMOVING USER INFORMATION**  
At any time and for any reason you may choose to correct or update your personal information by emailing us with your request at [privacy@gainsight.com](mailto:privacy@gainsight.com). If you choose to remove your data it will be deleted from our records within 90 days, but may remain in our archive or backup records for approximately 180 days.

 **DISPUTE RESOLUTION.** If you have any questions or comments about our use of information collected through the use of our website or Service, or about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@gainsight.com](mailto:privacy@gainsight.com). Gainsight will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you have regarding our use of such information and to comply fully with the legal and regulatory authorities responsible for enforcing our adherence to the privacy principles stated above.

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Gainsight is committed to resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EEA individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should contact Gainsight at:

Gainsight, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Shield Representative  
1400 Bridge Parkway Suite 101  
Redwood City, CA 94065  

Gainsight has further committed to refer unresolved complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to the BBB EU Privacy Shield, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you don’t receive timely acknowledgment of a complaint you have submitted, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information. If your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.** Gainsight may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post these changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. By using our website or Service you agree that we may also choose to contact you via the any email address that you have provided to us in order to notify you of any significant changes to this Privacy Policy.
